Finding Aid of the American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology Records, 1923-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1923-2015, UWM Manuscript Collection 139; 257.9 cubic ft. (741 boxes) 40 binders 1 oversize folder 30,895 digital files (79.5 GB) 1 film reel 4 safety film negatives
  - 4. Committees, Councils, and Interest Sections, 1944-2009
    - Marketing Task Force
      - American College of Allergists Payments, 1987 (Box 247, Folder 2)
      - Budget and Finance, 1986 (Box 247, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 247, Folder 4-7)
      - Marketing Program and Dues Assessment, 1985-1986 (Box 247, Folder 8)
      - Mass Media, 1986 (Box 247, Folder 9-10)
      - Mass Media, 1987 (Box 248, Folder 1)
      - Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 248, Folder 2)
      - National Opinion Poll, 1986 (Box 248, Folder 3)
      - Public Communications Inc., 1986, 1987 (Box 248, Folder 4-6)
      - Public Communications Inc., Contract, 1986 (Box 248, Folder 7)
      - Public Communications Inc., Media Training Seminars, 1986 (Box 248, Folder 8)
      - Public Communications Inc., Proposal, 1987 (Box 248, Folder 9)
      - Public Relations Programs, 1986 (Box 248, Folder 10)
      - Related Industries, 1986 (Box 248, Folder 11)
    - Marketing the Allergist
      - Joint Committee on (JCOMA), 1987 (Box 352, Folder 7)
      - Task Force on, 1987 (Box 246, Folder 11)
    - Mechanisms of Allergy Interest Section, 1988-1990 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Medical Informatics Committee, 1996-1999 (Box 572, Folder 11)
    - Medical Legislation and Socio-Economic Matters, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Medical Practice Services Committee
      - 1988 (Box 142, Folder 12)
      - 1989 (Box 248, Folder 12)
      - 1989-1995 (Box 142, Folder 13-15)
    - Medical Research Funding, Ad Hoc Group for, 1990-1991 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Medical Services Committee
      - 1967 (Box 142, Folder 16)
      - 1967-1973 (Box 143, Folder 1-9)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 144, Folder 1-4)
      - Relative Values Survey, 1970-1975 (Box 144, Folder 5-6)
    - Medicolegal Committee
      - 1988 (Box 114, Folder 6)
      - 1989-1995 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Metaproterenol
      - Ad Hoc Committee on, 1985 (Box 352, Folder 8-9)
      - undated (Box 374, Folder 1-2)
    - Military Allergy Committee, 1969-1989 (Box 144, Folder 8-12)
    - Mold Survey Committee, 1949-1961 (Box 145, Folder 1-2)
    - Multiple Chemical Sensitivity Committee
      - 1993 (Box 248, Folder 13-14)
      - Correspondence and Report, 1993-1996 (Box 445, Folder 34)
    - NAIC Committee, 2004 (Box 537, Folder 86)
    - Nasal Provocation Committee
      - 1987-1991 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Ad Hoc Committee on, 1982-1986 (Box 249, Folder 1-2)
    - National Allergists in Residence (NAIR) Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 592, Folder 6)
    - National Allergists in Residence (NAIR) Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 430, Folder 66-68)
    - National Allergists in Residence (NAIR) Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 384, Folder 8-9)
    - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases Relations, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1986-1988 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - National Institutes of Health/Food and Drug Administration Liaison Committee, 1992 (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - Nomenclature Committee, 1957-1964 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Nominating Committee
      - 1945-1977 (Box 145, Folder 5-6)
      - 1985-1988 (Box 145, Folder 7-10)
      - 1991-1999 (Box 592, Folder 7-11)
      - 1989-1990, 2004 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Non-Physician Education Committee, 1993 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Obituary Committee, 1954-1970 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Occupational Lung Disease Committee
      - 1982-1987 (Box 249, Folder 4-5)
      - 1988-1990 (Box 145, Folder 14-15)
      - 1991-1994 (Box 669, Folder 2)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 697, Folder 4)
    - Occupational Medicine Committee, 1991 (Box 145, Folder 16)
    - Outcomes Committee, 1995 (Box 352, Folder 10)
    - Over-the-Counter Metaproterenol, Ad Hoc Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 114, Folder 8-10)
    - Past Presidents Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 249, Folder 6)
    - Penicillin Study Group
      - 1966-1968 (Box 249, Folder 7)
      - 1971-1978 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - 1979-1988 (Box 249, Folder 8-9)
    - Petition for an Independent Certifying Board, Committee to, 1948 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Pharmaceutical Professional Relations Committee, 1992 (Box 249, Folder 10)
    - Physicians and Public Service Council
      - 1988-1990 (Box 146, Folder 2-3)
      - 1992 (Box 669, Folder 3-4)
      - 1994 (Box 249, Folder 11)
    - Pollen and Mold Committee
      - 1948-1953, 1960, 1966-1967, undated (Box 249, Folder 12)
      - 1970-1978 (Box 146, Folder 4-5)
      - 1979-1986 (Box 249, Folder 13-15)
      - 1987-1990 (Box 146, Folder 6-9)
    - Postgraduate Education Committee, 1951-1973 (Box 146, Folder 10-11)
    - Postgraduate Education Committee
      - 1951-1973 (Box 146, Folder 10-11)
      - 1974-1978 (Box 147, Folder 1-4)
      - 1985-1993 (Box 147, Folder 5-9)
      - Handbook, 1978 (Box 249, Folder 16-17)
      - Handbook, 1978 (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - Practice Parameters, Joint Task Force, 1993 (Box 445, Folder 35)
    - Practice Parameters, Joint Task Force, 1990-1992, 1995 (Box 250, Folder 2-4)
    - Practice Standards
      - 1987-1989 (Box 251, Folder 1-6)
      - 1990 (Box 252, Folder 1-2)
      - 1991 (Box 147, Folder 11-13)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 250, Folder 5-9)
      - 1994 (Box 147, Folder 10)
      - 1994 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 592, Folder 12)
      - 1996-2001 (Box 543, Folder 29)
      - Abusive Practices, 1985 (Box 361, Folder 1)
      - Barsel Method, 1982-1984 (Box 361, Folder 2)
      - Bee Pollen, 1985 (Box 361, Folder 3)
      - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 361, Folder 4)
      - Clinical Ecology Symposia, 1984 (Box 362, Folder 3)
      - Clinical Ecology, 1983-1986 (Box 361, Folder 7-12)
      - Clinical Ecology, 1987-1988 (Box 362, Folder 1-2)
      - Coalition on Regulation of Physician's Office Labs, 1985 (Box 361, Folder 6)
      - Controversial Techniques, 1985-1986 (Box 362, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence & Minutes, 1999 (Box 592, Folder 15)
      - Practice Standards Council, 2000 (Box 592, Folder 17)
      - Electrodermal Diagnosis, 1985 (Box 362, Folder 5)
      - Environmental Chemical Sensitivity Syndrome, 1984 (Box 362, Folder 6)
      - Food Allergy Tests, 1986 (Box 362, Folder 8)
      - Food Immune Complex Assay, 1985 (Box 362, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 362, Folder 9-13)
      - General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 363, Folder 1)
      - Genetic and Therapeutic Substitution of Drugs, 1986 (Box 361, Folder 5)
      - Health Insurance Association of America, 1984-1985 (Box 363, Folder 2)
      - Hospital Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 363, Folder 3)
      - IgE Food Immune Complex Assay (FICA), 1986 (Box 363, Folder 4)
      - Immune Disorders, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 363, Folder 5)
      - Immune Milk, 1983 (Box 363, Folder 6)
      - Insurance Company Correspondence, 1983-1989 (Box 363, Folder 7)
      - Insurance Company Correspondence, 1992 (Box 592, Folder 13)
      - Mail Order Allergy, Cytotoxic Testing, 1983-1985 (Box 363, Folder 9)
      - Mail Order Allergy, RAST, 1982-1983 (Box 363, Folder 10)
      - Mail Order Allergy, RAST, 1984-1988 (Box 364, Folder 1-3)
      - MAST Immunosystems, 1984-1988 (Box 364, Folder 4-7)
      - Mayo Clinic/Johns Hopkins In Vitro Testing, 1985 (Box 363, Folder 8)
      - Medic Alert, 1985 (Box 364, Folder 8)
      - Medical Malpractice, 1986 (Box 364, Folder 9)
      - Medical Marketing Forum, 1984 (Box 365, Folder 1)
      - Metpath, 1985 (Box 365, Folder 2)
      - Monaco, Grace P., 1984-1985 (Box 365, Folder 3)
      - Otolaryngology, 1983-1986 (Box 365, Folder 4)
      - Peer Review, 1985 (Box 365, Folder 5)
      - Policy for Reimbursement for Appropriate Management of Allergic or Immunologic Diseases, 1984-1985 (Box 365, Folder 6)
      - Position Statements, Correspondence, 1977-1984 (Box 365, Folder 7-10)
      - Pre-Measured Ephedrine, 1984 (Box 365, Folder 12)
      - Professional Review Organizations (PRO), 1984 (Box 365, Folder 11)
      - Provocation-Neutralization Technique, 1984 (Box 365, Folder 13)
      - Rae vs. AAAI, 1982-1986 (Box 365, Folder 14)
      - Rae vs. AAAI, 1982-1986 (Box 366, Folder 1-3)
      - Rapp, Doris, 1985 (Box 366, Folder 4)
      - Remote Practice of Allergy, Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 445, Folder 36)
      - Remote Practice, 1992-1993 (Box 592, Folder 14)
      - Remote Practice of Allergy, Correspondence, 1987-1991, 1994 (Box 445, Folder 37)
      - Rodreguez vs. U.S. Dept. of the Treasury, 1986 (Box 366, Folder 5)
      - Roybal Request, 1985 (Box 366, Folder 6)
      - Skin Tests, 1984 (Box 366, Folder 7)
      - State Medical Associations, 1985 (Box 366, Folder 8)
      - State of Minnesota Case, 1984-1985 (Box 366, Folder 9)
      - Stevens Johnson Syndrome, 1986 (Box 366, Folder 10)
      - Sublingual Immunotherapy Great Britain Study, 1986-1988 (Box 366, Folder 11)
      - Sublingual Provocative Testing, 1980 (Box 366, Folder 12)
      - Systemic Reactions Position Statement, 1983-1986 (Box 366, Folder 13)
      - Therapeutics, 1999 (Box 592, Folder 16)
      - Units of Measurement for Patient Care, 1984 (Box 366, Folder 14)
      - Unproven Procedures, 1985 (Box 366, Folder 15)
      - Ventrex Laboratories, 1986 (Box 366, Folder 16)
    - President's Grants-in-Aid, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Primary Care Rotations in Allergy and Pierson Visitation Program Committee, 1999-2001, 2004 (Box 537, Folder 88)
    - Professional Development Committee, 1988-1993 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Professional Education Council
      - 1988-1989 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - 1993 (Box 669, Folder 5)
      - 1994 (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - 1999 (Box 543, Folder 36)
    - Professional Information Committee
      - 1987-1989 (Box 148, Folder 4-8)
      - 1989 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - 1989 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - 1990-1996 (Box 149, Folder 2-8)
      - Kimberly-Clark, 1991-1992 (Box 149, Folder 9)
      - Kleenex, 1988 (Box 149, Folder 10)
      - Kleenex, 1989 (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - Marketing the Allergist Survey, 1988-1989 (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - Membership Recruitment Video, 1988-1989 (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - Physician Referral Line, 1987-1989 (Box 150, Folder 4-6)
      - TV Public Service Announcements, 1984-1988 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Professional Information for Allergists Subcommittee, 1993-1994 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Professional Information for Industry Subcommittee, 1989-1991 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Professional Information for Pharmacists Subcommittee, 1992-1993 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Professional Lay Organizations Task Force, 1994-1995 (Box 592, Folder 5)
    - Professional Standards, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1969-1972 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Program Committee
      - 1961-1969 (Box 150, Folder 11)
      - 1972-1979 (Box 150, Folder 12-13)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - 1985-1987 (Box 151, Folder 2-4)
      - 1989 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - 1992 (Box 520, Folder 31)
      - Score Sheets, 1982-1983 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Protection of Animal Research, Committee on, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Protection of Animals in Research, Committee for, 1989-1990 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Public Affairs and Membership Services Division, Notes, 1991 (Box 461, Folder 4)
    - Public Affairs, Task Force on
      - 1982-1984 (Box 164, Folder 6-7)
      - 1985 (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - Public Education and Program Planning, Joint Steering Committee, 1987 (Box 352, Folder 11)
    - Public Education Committee
      - 1982-1983 (Box 151, Folder 7-9)
      - 1983-1987 (Box 152, Folder 1-7)
      - 1988-1990 (Box 153, Folder 1-3)
      - 1994-1997 (Box 463, Folder 8)
      - Advocate, 1983-1986 (Box 153, Folder 4-8)
      - Advocate, Subscriptions, 1986 (Box 153, Folder 9)
      - Advocate, Subscriptions, 1986 (Box 154, Folder 1-2)
      - Allergy Self Help Book, 1986 (Box 154, Folder 3)
      - Annual Meeting Publicity, 1985 (Box 154, Folder 4-7)
      - Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 154, Folder 8)
      - Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 155, Folder 1-2)
      - Asthma and Allergy Alert Newsletter, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 3-4)
      - Expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 155, Folder 5-6)
      - Food Booklet Funding, 1986 (Box 155, Folder 7)
      - Guidelines for the Asthmatic Child in the School Setting, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 8)
      - Hollister-Stier Allergy Video, 1985-1986 (Box 155, Folder 9)
      - Hometown Radio Interviews, 1986 (Box 155, Folder 10)
      - Information, 1986 (Box 155, Folder 11)
      - Information, 1986 (Box 156, Folder 1)
      - Joint Steering Committee, 1986 (Box 156, Folder 2)
      - Lay Version of Food Monograph, 1984-1986 (Box 156, Folder 3-6)
      - Lifetime Information, 1984 (Box 373, Folder 1-2)
      - Lifetime Medical Programming, 1984 (Box 373, Folder 3)
      - Lifetime Medical Programming, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 7)
      - Media Inquiries, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 8)
      - Media Training Workshop, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 9)
      - News Releases, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 10)
      - Newsview Galleys, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 11)
      - Operations Manual, 1981-1982 (Box 252, Folder 7)
      - Pharmacist Link, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 12)
      - Public Education Survey, 1998 (Box 490, Folder 17)
      - Public Opinion Survey, 1984 (Box 373, Folder 4-5)
      - Public Opinion Survey, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 13)
      - Public Service Announcements, 1984 (Box 373, Folder 6-7)
      - Tips to Remember Series, 1984 (Box 156, Folder 14)
      - Tips to Remember Series, 1985-1986 (Box 157, Folder 1-3)
      - TV Guide Advertisement, 1984 (Box 373, Folder 8)
      - Weather Channel, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Public Information and Education on Acceptable Medical Practices, Subcommittee on
      - 1988 (Box 163, Folder 21)
      - 1989 (Box 252, Folder 8)
    - Public Relations Committee
      - 1957-1978 (Box 157, Folder 5-8)
      - Activities for Annual Meeting, 1956-1970 (Box 252, Folder 9)
    - Quality of Care for Asthma Committee
      - 1988 (Box 157, Folder 9)
      - 1989-1995 (Box 158, Folder 1-2)
    - Questionable Techniques and Practices, Correspondence and Position Statements, 1971-1975 (Box 445, Folder 37)
    - RAST Mini Collaborative Study, Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 445, Folder 38)
    - Regional, State, and Local Allergy Societies
      - Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 252, Folder 10)
      - Council, 1973-1975 (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - Council, 1987-1989 (Box 158, Folder 4-6)
      - Council, 1991 (Box 158, Folder 7-9)
      - Council, 1992 (Box 373, Folder 9)
      - Council, 1996 (Box 463, Folder 9)
      - Liaison Committee, 1973-1981 (Box 159, Folder 1-4)
      - Liaison Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 159, Folder 5-7)
      - Liaison Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 160, Folder 1-4)
      - Membership, 1992 (Box 253, Folder 1-2)
      - Strategic Roundtable, 2000 (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - Rehabilitation Committee
      - 1987-1988 (Box 160, Folder 5-6)
      - 1992 (Box 455, Folder 19)
    - Rehabilitation Therapy and Sports Medicine, Committee on, 1986 (Box 253, Folder 5)
    - Rehabilitation Therapy Committee
      - 1964-1968 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      - 1971-1978 (Box 160, Folder 7)
      - 1980-1985 (Box 253, Folder 4)
    - Related Industries Committee, 1987-1995 (Box 253, Folder 6-7)
    - Related Industries Council, Educational Projects Budget Proposal, 1987 (Box 253, Folder 8)
    - Related Organizations Committee
      - 1989 (Box 160, Folder 8)
      - 1993 (Box 253, Folder 9)
    - Reorganization of the Academy, Ad Hoc Committee, 1985-1988 (Box 114, Folder 13-16)
    - Reorganization of the Academy, Ad Hoc Committee
      - 1985 (Box 114, Folder 17)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 592, Folder 19)
    - Research Advisory Council, 2000-2001 (Box 679, Folder 9)
    - Research and Training Subcommittee, 1998-2002 (Box 679, Folder 10)
    - Research Council
      - 1949-1962 (Box 160, Folder 9-11)
      - 1963-1976 (Box 161, Folder 1-7)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 162, Folder 1)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 253, Folder 10)
      - 1986 (Box 253, Folder 11)
      - 1987-1990 (Box 162, Folder 2-4)
      - 1994 (Box 253, Folder 12)
      - Committee Appointments, 1975 (Box 162, Folder 5)
      - Roster, 1964-1982 (Box 253, Folder 13)
    - Resource Development, Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 124, Folder 11-12)
    - Review of Allergenic Products, Ad Hoc Committee for, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 446, Folder 1)
    - Review of Questionnaire and Survey, Ad Hoc Committee for, 1975 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Rhinitis, Committee on, 1988-1989, 1996 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Role and Care of Animals in Research, Committee on, 1989-1993 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Scientific and Educational Council, 1950-1951 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Scientific and Educational Fund Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Scientific Exhibits and Workshop Committee
      - Handbook, 1975 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - 1959-1978 (Box 162, Folder 8-12)
      - 1985-1991 (Box 163, Folder 1-4)
    - Seminar Subcommittee, 2004 (Box 537, Folder 89)
    - Seminars Committee
      - 1985-1989 (Box 163, Folder 5-8)
      - Operations Manual, 1982-1983 (Box 254, Folder 2)
    - Sinusitis Committee, 1993 (Box 455, Folder 20)
    - Socio-Economics of Allergy, Joint Council of, 1975-1976 (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - Specialty Boards Meeting, Liaison Committee for, 1968-1971 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Specific Therapy Committee
      - 1948-1960 (Box 254, Folder 4)
      - 1972-1975 (Box 163, Folder 10)
      - Food and Drug Administration Deliberations, 1973 (Box 446, Folder 2)
    - Specific Therapy, Subcommittee on, 1961-1968 (Box 163, Folder 22)
    - Sports Medicine Committee
      - 1987-1991 (Box 163, Folder 11)
      - 1991-2001 (Box 697, Folder 5-6)
      - Exercise Induces Asthma, EIA Protocol, 2000-2001 (Box 697, Folder 7)
    - Standards of Care for Asthma, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1987-1988 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Sulfite and Food Additive Sensitivities Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 669, Folder 6)
    - Symposia Subcommittee, 2004 (Box 537, Folder 87)
    - Task Force for Evaluation of Non-Bronchodilator, Anti-Asthmatic Drugs
      - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 446, Folder 3)
      - Workshop Papers, 1986 (Box 446, Folder 4)
    - Therapy, Committee on, 1947-1950 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Training Program Directors
      - Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 386, Folder 4)
      - Minutes, Annual Retreat, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 447, Folder 24)
      - National Issues Subcommittee, 1996-1998 (Box 534, Folder 36)
      - Retreat
        - 1989 (Box 386, Folder 7)
        - 1998 (Box 543, Folder 25)
        - Workshop Reports, 1995, 1998 (Box 534, Folder 34)
      - Committee
        - 1985-1988 (Box 164, Folder 8-11)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 165, Folder 1-2)
        - 1991-1994 (Box 254, Folder 5-7)
        - 1995 (Box 373, Folder 10)
        - Case History Module Exercise, undated (Box 254, Folder 8-9)
        - Merck Correspondence
          - 1997 (Box 592, Folder 20)
          - 1996-1997 (Box 592, Folder 21)
    - Training Program Directors Executive Committee
      - 1996-1997 (Box 534, Folder 35)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 679, Folder 11)
    - Undergraduate and Graduate Education Committee
      - 1964-1969 (Box 165, Folder 3-4)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 165, Folder 5)
      - 1985-1988 (Box 165, Folder 6-9)
      - Handbook, 1975 (Box 255, Folder 1)
      - Travel Grants, 1963-1975 (Box 166, Folder 5-6)
    - Undergraduate and Graduate Medical Education Committee
      - 1989-1992 (Box 165, Folder 10)
      - 1993-1996 (Box 166, Folder 1-4)
      - Pierson Lectureships, 1992-1998 (Box 543, Folder 32)
    - Underrepresented Minorities Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 679, Folder 12)
    - Upper Airway Allergy Committee
      - 1989-1991 (Box 166, Folder 7-8)
      - Rhinopharyngolaryngoscopy Report, 1992 (Box 446, Folder 5)
    - Urticaria Committee
      - 1993-2001 (Box 669, Folder 7)
      - 2002-2004, 2005 (Box 679, Folder 13-14)
    - Veterans Administration Allergy Committee, 1989 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Veterans Administration Hospital Allergists, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Veterans Affairs Committee, 1990-1995 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Weather and Air Pollution Committee
      - 1962-1966 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - 1970-1978 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Weather, Committee on, 1963-1964 (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - Women's Involvement in AAAAI Affairs Committee, 1996, 2004 (Box 526, Folder 7)
    - Workforce Committee, 1995, 1996 (Box 168, Folder 1-2)
    - Workshop Committee, 1988, 1999-2002 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - 5. Related Organizations, 1947-2008
    This series contains correspondence and related information on the Academy's relationship with organizations that work within the fields of allergy, asthma, and immunology. Much information can be found regarding the American Board of Allergy and Immunology, American College of Allergy, Asthma and Immunology, and the Asthma and Allergy Foundation of America.
    - Abbott Laboratories, 1989-1992 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Accreditation Council for Continuing Medical Education
      - 1984-1988 (Box 170, Folder 7)
      - 1991-1995 (Box 170, Folder 8)
      - Essentials and Guidelines for Accreditation of Sponsors of Continuing Medical Education and Standards for Commercial Support and Enduring Materials, undated (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - Adams Laboratories, 1987-1992 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Advisory Committee on Childhood Vaccines, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Allen and Hansbury, 1989-1992 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Allergy and Asthma Network
      - 1993-1994 (Box 170, Folder 12-13)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 171, Folder 1-2)
    - Allergy and Asthma Network/Mothers of Asthmatics
      - I'm a Meter Reader, 1994 (Box 490, Folder 5)
      - The New Asthma Organizer, 1994 (Box 446, Folder 6)
      - Proposals, 1996-2000 (Box 670, Folder 1)
    - Allergy, Asthma, and Immunology, Education and Research Trust, Meeting, 2007-2008 (Box 721, Folder 4-5)
    - Allergy Asthma Information Association, 1985-1995 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Allergy Foundation of America, 1965-1975 (Box 201, Folder 7-8)
    - Allergy Testing Association, 1990 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Allertec, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - ALK Laboratories, 1988-1992 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Alliance for Continuing Medical Education, 1985-1989 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1989 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - American Academy of Dermatology, 1983-1994 (Box 171, Folder 9-12)
    - American Academy of Environmental Medicine, 1984-1990 (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - American Academy of Family Physicians
      - 1987-1990 (Box 171, Folder 14)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 172, Folder 1-2)
    - American Academy of Ophthalmology, 1987-1995 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - American Academy of Orthopaedic Surgeons, 1982-1993 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - American Academy of Otolaryngic Allergy, 1983-1995 (Box 172, Folder 5-7)
    - American Academy of Otolaryngology, Head and Neck Surgery
      - 1982-1984 (Box 172, Folder 8-10)
      - 1984-1994 (Box 173, Folder 1-2)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics, 1984-1996 (Box 173, Folder 3-6)
    - American Academy of Physician Assistants, 1994 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - American Allergy Association, 1985 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - American Association for Allergy and Clinical Immunology, 1976-1986 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - American Association for Medical Education, 1987 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - American Association of Bioethics, 1993 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - American Association of Certified Allergists, 1977-1994 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - American Association of Immunologists, 1983-1994 (Box 174, Folder 2-4)